milesfaster.co.uk 2016-04-16

# Milesfaster.co.uk privacy policy.

This is the website of [www.milesfaster.co.uk](https://www.milesfaster.co.uk/)  
We can be contacted using the form >>>here

At milesfaster.co.uk we take your privacy as seriously as you would yourself. Below we explain the types of information we collect, why we collect it and at what stage this information is gathered.

For each visitor to our Website, our Web server (the computer on which our website is served from) automatically recognises your IP addresses (known as internet protocol), your browser type, referring/exit pages (often blocked on the client side by your security software) and operating system. The information is coated and stored in server log files and this is normal practice for standard websites (just about every commercial website on the internet). These logs are stored for one month and then securely deleted.   
This information is not linked to personally identifiable information or data.  
The data we gather in this way is used for internal review only to help improve the website experience and the information is then securely electronically deleted after one month.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail to more efficiently deal with that current and any further correspondence from that client. We do not sell, rent or trade that information to any other party.

For any personal information supplied to us electronically or other by other means, you will only receive communication in connection with, and relevant to, that original correspondence.

If you make a hotel booking through this website you will be asked for the following information: Name, home or work telephone number, fax number, email address, credit card number and its expiration date, and your credit card billing address.  
If you make a reservation for other people you will be asked for identifiable information for these other parties. You should obtain permission from these individuals to provide their information.   
The information is necessary in order to process your reservation and confirm back to you that this has been successfully completed. The information is then used to identify you should you wish to query and/or change details of your reservation. 

Cookies (text files placed on your hard drive): These are used to record session information only at the point you choose to click through a booking/quote request page. This website does not use cookies until the client has chosen to click through a rates check page.  
The information stored is used to speed up the user experience by means such as auto filling requested dates and logins.

  We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. 

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries).

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information.

Security: When sensitive information is requested such as credit card numbers SSL secure encrypted transmission is used. This is signified by the prefix https in your browser address bar and a padlock/security logo in your browser window.

External links: At various points of our website we link out to external websites. Normally these are for information purposes. Our privacy policy covers our website only and for external websites you should check their individual privacy policy.
